Guide to the Kingsley Memorial Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- WILLIAM L. KINGSLEY PAPERS, 1830-1898; Series II; 2.5' (6 boxes)
  - Personal papers
    - Journal, 1855 (Box 11, Folder 531-532)
    - Miscellanea, undated (Box 11, Folder 533)
- FAMILY PAPERS, 1696/1697-1934; Series III; 2' (5 boxes)
  This series is arranged in alphabetical order by the name of the creator of the material.
  - Adams, Nathaniel, 1828 (Box 12, Folder 534)
  - Adams, Sarah, 1814 (Box 12, Folder 535)
  - Addison, Julie H., undated (Box 12, Folder 536)
  - Armitage, William E.
    See: box 18, folder 763
  - Atterbury, William Wallace, 1862, 1869 (Box 12, Folder 537)
  - Bacon, David, 1874, undated (Box 12, Folder 538)
  - Bartlette, Shubad, 1853 (Box 12, Folder 539)
  - Bates, Anna Maria (Upham), 1858-1872 (Box 12, Folder 540-543)
  - Bates, Anna Maria (Upham) and George Upham, 1848, 1853 (Box 12, Folder 544)
  - Bates, John, 1867 (Box 12, Folder 545)
  - Bates, Laura, 1875, 1879 (Box 12, Folder 546)
  - Bates, Loulie, 1861-1879, undated (Box 12, Folder 547-548)
  - Bates, Morris Upham, 1877 (Box 12, Folder 549)
  - Beck, Charles, 1845 (Box 12, Folder 550)
  - Blake, Elizabeth Coit (Kingsley), 1862-1870, undated (Box 12, Folder 551-552)
  - Blake, Henry T., 1918 (Box 12, Folder 553)
  - Blake, Henry W., 1887 (Box 12, Folder 554)
  - Boalt, Charles S., 1842 (Box 12, Folder 555)
  - Brewster, Joseph, [1892?] (Box 12, Folder 556)
  - Brodhead, J.R., 1857 (Box 12, Folder 557)
  - Buck, Dudley, Jr., 1864 (Box 12, Folder 558)
  - Buck, Mrs. M.C., undated (Box 12, Folder 559)
  - Capela, John, Jr., 1853 (Box 12, Folder 560)
  - Chandler, Elizabeth Douglas, 1696/7 (Box 12, Folder 561)
  - Clark, Martha Upham, 1868, 1869, undated (Box 12, Folder 562-564)
  - Clarke, I. Edwards, 1875 (Box 12, Folder 565)
  - Clemson, Thomas, G., 1829 (Box 12, Folder 566)
  - Coit, Daniel L., 1828-1830, undated (Box 12, Folder 567-569)
    See also: box 14, folder 671
  - Coit, Daniel W., 1824 (Box 12, Folder 570)
  - Coit, Henry H., 1861 (Box 12, Folder 571)
  - Coit, Joshua, 1725 (Box 12, Folder 572)
  - Coit, Joshua, Last Will and Testament of Joshua Coit, of New Haven, Conn., 1881 (Box 12, Folder 572a)
  - Colby, Carry, 1857-1859 (Box 12, Folder 573)
  - Cooley, James, 1863 (Box 12, Folder 574)
  - Crane, Anna F., 1869 (Box 12, Folder 575)
  - Creighton, I., 1828, undated (Box 12, Folder 576)
  - Dana, Henrietta Silliman, [1862?] (Box 12, Folder 577)
  - Dana, L., 1891 (Box 12, Folder 578)
  - Eccely, B.A., 1891 (Box 12, Folder 579)
  - Ely, David, Jr., 1805 (Box 12, Folder 580)
  - Ely, Eliza Adams Upham, 1869 (Box 12, Folder 581)
  - Everett, Edward, 1825, 1853 (Box 12, Folder 582)
  - Farnam, Elizabeth Upham (Kingsley), 1866-1885, undated (Box 12, Folder 583-588)
    See also: box 13, folders 620-623
  - Farnam, Henry, 1873-1920 (Box 12, Folder 589-590)
  - Fiske, Samuel, 1859 (Box 12, Folder 591)
  - Fleischmann, ____, 1811 (Box 12, Folder 592)
  - Fox, Sissy, 1869 (Box 12, Folder 593)
  - Gibbons, Louisa, undated (Box 12, Folder 594)
  - Gilman, Daniel Coit, 1855-1900 (Box 12, Folder 595-600)
  - Gilman, Eliza Coit, undated (Box 12, Folder 601)
  - Gilman, William Charles, 1842 (Box 12, Folder 602)
  - Gladwin, Mary F., undated (Box 12, Folder 603)
  - Goodrich, Chauncey Allen, 1855 (Box 12, Folder 604)
  - Graffenrid, Clare de, 1901 (Box 12, Folder 605)
  - Greenleaf, P.H., 1849-1955 (Box 12, Folder 606-608)
  - Hall, Caro L.R., 1855, 1869 (Box 12, Folder 609)
  - Harper, Robert Francis, undated (Box 12, Folder 610)
  - Herrick, Edward Claudius, 1860 (Box 12, Folder 611)
  - Hubbard, Henrietta Whitney, 1873 (Box 12, Folder 612)
  - Hubbell, Louise, 1861-1869, n.d (Box 12, Folder 613)
  - Hubbell, Peter, 1861-1863 (Box 12, Folder 614)
  - Hutchings, Elizabeth L., 1834 (Box 12, Folder 615)
  - Jaques, Maria, 1853 (Box 12, Folder 616)
  - Johnson, Elizabeth Erwin (Blinn), 1872 (Box 12, Folder 617)
  - Kettell, C.H., [1869?] (Box 13, Folder 618)
  - Kingsley, Cornelia, 1840, 1842 (Box 13, Folder 619)
  - Kingsley, Elizabeth Upham (Mrs. Henry W. Farnam), 1888-1929 (Box 13, Folder 620-623)
  - Kingsley, Emily, 1853, undated (Box 13, Folder 624)
  - Kingsley, George, 1879 (Box 13, Folder 625)
  - Kingsley, George Theodore, 1818-1842 (Box 13, Folder 626-633)
  - Kingsley, Henry Coit, 1833-1885 (Box 13, Folder 634-641)
  - Kingsley, H. Louise Upham, 1835-1854 (Box 13, Folder 642-645)
  - Kingsley, H. Louise Upham, 1843-1874 (Box 14, Folder 646-647)
    See also: box 18, folder 764
  - Kingsley, J.L., 1880-1900 (Box 14, Folder 648)
  - Kingsley, James L., 1801-1852 (Box 14, Folder 649-651)
    See also: box 14, folder 671 box 18, folder 765
  - Kingsley, Jane Thomas Handy, 1852-1869, undated (Box 14, Folder 652-655)
  - Kingsley, Jeannie Taylor, 1899, 1930 (Box 14, Folder 656-657)
  - Kingsley, Lewis, 1879-1880 (Box 14, Folder 658)
  - Kingsley, Lydia Coit, 1824-1846, undated (Box 14, Folder 659-663)
  - Kingsley, Mary, 1901 (Box 14, Folder 664)
  - Kingsley, V.W., 1854 (Box 14, Folder 665)
  - Kingsley, William L., 1805-1878 (Box 14, Folder 666)
  - Kingsley family
    - Correspondence, 1822-1888 (Box 14, Folder 667)
    - Diary extracts, [ca. 1860] (Box 14, Folder 668)
    - Genealogy, [ca. 1834-1934] (Box 14, Folder 669-670)
    - Wills, 1833-1853 (Box 14, Folder 671)
    - Miscellanea, 1821-1878, undated (Box 14, Folder 672)
  - Knight Martha K., undated (Box 14, Folder 673)
  - Lane, Louisa G., 1897 (Box 15, Folder 674)
  - Lathrop, Daniel Coit, 1783 (Box 15, Folder 675)
  - Lathrop, Lydia, 1809, undated (Box 15, Folder 676)
  - Lawrence, Amos A., 1849 (Box 15, Folder 677)
  - Leffingwell, William, 1810 (Box 15, Folder 678)
  - Lieber, Francis, undated (Box 15, Folder 679)
  - Mandell, Alice C., 1870 (Box 15, Folder 680)
  - Mantell, Gideon Algernon, 1839, undated (Box 15, Folder 681)
  - Mason, Jeremiah, 1828, undated (Box 15, Folder 682)
  - Miller, James, 1814 (Box 15, Folder 683)
  - Morse, Lucretia Pickering Walker, 1822 (Box 15, Folder 684)
  - Nevins, William, 1827 (Box 15, Folder 685)
  - Parker, Caroline E., 1869 (Box 15, Folder 686)
  - Peck, William Stedman, 1849 (Box 15, Folder 687)
  - Perit, Maria Coit, 1836-1884, undated (Box 15, Folder 688-691)
  - Plumer, William, 1819 (Box 15, Folder 692)
  - Porter, Delia Lyman, 1890, 1891 (Box 15, Folder 693)
  - Porter, Noah, 1852 (Box 15, Folder 694)
  - Rives, William Cabell, 1839 (Box 15, Folder 695)
  - Sanford, James Hervey, 1835 (Box 15, Folder 696)
  - Silliman, Benjamin, Sr., 1813 (Box 15, Folder 697)
  - Snelling, Josiah, 1814 (Box 15, Folder 698)
  - Sparhawk, Deborah Adams, 1813, 1814 (Box 15, Folder 699-700)
  - Stimson, Henry Albert, 1865-1869 (Box 15, Folder 701)
  - Thacher, Joseph H., 1860 (Box 15, Folder 702)
  - Thacher, Thomas Anthony, 1852 (Box 15, Folder 703)
  - Thompson, Elizabeth Coit Gilman, undated (Box 15, Folder 704)
  - Thompson, George, 1849 (Box 15, Folder 705)
  - Thompson, John H., 1863 (Box 15, Folder 706)
  - Ullman, Daniel, 1880 (Box 15, Folder 707)
  - U.S. Army, 1812-1825 (Box 15, Folder 708)
  - U.S. Department of War, 1815 (Box 15, Folder 709)
  - Upham, Charlotte Mary, 1852-1869 (Box 15, Folder 710-716)
  - Upham, E. W., 1864 (Box 15, Folder 717)
  - Upham, Eliza Adams, 1811-1852, undated (Box 15, Folder 718-724)
    See also: box 15, folder 700 box 17, folder 760-762
  - Upham, F. Morris, 1842-1852, undated (Box 15, Folder 725-730)
  - Upham, George Timothy, 1839-1853 (Box 16, Folder 731-734)
  - Upham, Hannah, 1842, 1869-1905 (Box 16, Folder 735)
  - Upham, Sarah, 1853-1869 (Box 16, Folder 736)
  - Upham, Timothy, 1804-1854 (Box 16, Folder 737-742)
    See also: box 17, folders 760-762 box 18, folder 766
  - Upham family, undated (Box 16, Folder 743)
  - Webster, Daniel, 1827, 1846 (Box 16, Folder 744-745)
  - Webster, Grace, 1824, undated (Box 16, Folder 746)
  - Welch, Joseph Ashley, 1852 (Box 16, Folder 747)
  - Woodbridge, L. A., undated (Box 16, Folder 748)
  - Woodbury, Levi, 1828, 1842 (Box 16, Folder 749)
  - Woolsey, Sarah, undated (Box 16, Folder 750)
  - Worcester, Edwin Dean, Jr., 1901 (Box 16, Folder 751)
  - Miscellanea, undated (Box 16, Folder 752-757)
- OVERSIZE
  - Hoadley, George, 1806-1807 (Box 17, Folder 758)
  - Kingsley, James L.: daybook, 1833-1852 (Box 17, Folder 759)
  - Upham, Eliza and Timothy: photostats of letters, 1812-1815 (Box 17, Folder 760-762)
  - Armitage, William, 1810-1841 (Box 18, Folder 763)
    Folio
  - Kingsley, H. Louise Upham, 1857, 1884 (Box 18, Folder 764)
  - Kingsley, James Luce, 1826-1847 (Box 18, Folder 765)
  - Upham, Timothy, 1810-1841 (Box 18, Folder 766)
  - Clippings, [ca. 1834-1857] (Box 18, Folder 767)